Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design,Corcoran Gallery of Art education department records 1961-2010 COR0006.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administration files [2016 processing project], Circa 1963 - Circa 2012; Series 14
  - [Unlabeled Cassette Tape], Circa 1984-2002; Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Catlett Lecture (Cassette Tape), Circa 1984-2002; Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Andrew Stevovich Lecture 2001 Cassette Tape, Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Readers Circle: The New Negro Movement, 1998; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Readers Circle: Salon Dore & Enlightenment, Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Readers Circle: Hopper & Thomas Mann, Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Bierstadt, Albert "The Last of the Buffalo" - Cooper, James Fenimore "The Last of the Mohicans", Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - [Readers Circle "Dialogue with Nature", Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Readers Circle: The Sublime (Landscape & Literature), Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Readers Circle: Joan Arc, Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - [Readers Circle: Harlem Renaissance], Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Readers Circle, 1997-1998; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Readers Circle: Lists, Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - [Lois Mailou Jones], Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Readers Circle: Satire (Daumier), Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Heroes & Heroines, Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Readers Circle: African Americans, Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Readers Circle: Weaving a Tale, Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Edith Wharton/John Singer Sargent, Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Cecilia Beaux, Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Book Club: Readers Circle, 1996; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Vaclav Havel: Words, Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Naked and Nude, Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - [Loose Documents], Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Reader's Circle, 1996; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Reader's Circle, Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - AAM '95: Marketplaace, 1995; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - [Loose Readers Circle], Circa 1994-1999; Series 14 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - January Daily Visitor Sheets, Circa 2005-2011; Series 14 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Deposit Record 2005, Series 14 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Corcoran Gallery Admission Daily Deposit Reports, Circa 2005-2011; Series 14 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - First Half Apr 2005, 2005 January 1-15; Series 14 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - 1st Half Apr 2006, 2006 February 16-28; Series 14 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - 2nd Half Apr 2006, 2006 June 1-15; Series 14 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Ticketmaster Washington DC Final Settlement Detail, 2006; Series 14 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Modernism Sales Activitiees Reports 2007-, Series 14 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Time Sheets 2004-2005, Series 14 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Time Sheets 2006, Series 14 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Accounting of Vouchers 2007, Series 14 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Avedon and other Educational Materials, 2008-2009; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Promised Land, 1980; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - In Response to Place Educator Resource, 2001; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - In Response to Place, 2001; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - 44th Biennial (1), 1995; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - 44th Biennial (2), 1995; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Quilts of Gee's Bend Educator Resource Packet, 2004; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Rhapsodies in Black and other Education Programs, 1998; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - African American Art Education Pack, Undated; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Emmet Gowin 3 Packets, 2002; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Painters in the American West, 2001; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Jasper Johns to Jeff Koons In Response to Place, 2001-2002; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Ansel Adams Inner Visions, 2007-2012; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Youth Family Packets, 2012; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Antiquities to Impressionism Educator Resource, 2001; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Summer Teacher Institute, 2011; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - ArtReach In School Lesson Plans, Undated; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Summer Teacher Institute Down Through Generations, 2012; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Educator Institute Art Social Justice, 2013; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Encourageing American Genius, Undated; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Docent Handbooks, 1993-2003; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Docent Handbooks, 1994-1996; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Docent Issues, 2004-2005; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Modernism - Family Guides, Undated; Series 14 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - 44th Biennial, 1995; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Teaching from Photographs, 1995; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Raised by Wolves, 1995; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Africa Express, 1988; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Fables, Folktales and Myths, 1996; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - The Peale Family Bourgeois, 1994-1997; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Picturing History, 1994; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Roy DeCarava, 1998-1999; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Picturing the Past New World's From Old, 1999; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Silent Subjects Ellis Ruley, 1994-1995; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Loose Family Programs, Undated; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Discover the Corcoran, Undated; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Family Day, 1995 October; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Bourgeouis Leisure and Labor, 1994; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Promised Land, Undated; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Sons of My People Hospice, 1990-1996; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Gordon Parks and SNCC, 1996; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Architecture is Elementary Tour Materials, Undated; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - American Masters, Dialogue with Nature, We the People, Undated; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Architecture is Elementary, 1979; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Face to Face (early), Undated; Series 14 (Box 67, Folder 21)
- Admissions files [2016 processing project], 2008-2011; Series 15
  - Admissions Desk Daily Control Sheets September 2010, 2010 September; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Admissions Desk Daily Control Sheets October 2010, 2010 October; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Admissions Desk Daily Control Sheets November 2010, 2010 November; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Admissions Desk Daily Control Sheets December 2010, 2010 December; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Admissions Desk Daily Control Sheets January 2011, 2011 January; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Admissions Desk Daily Control Sheets February 2011, 2011 February; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Admissions Desk Daily Control Sheets March 2011, 2011 March; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Admissions Desk Daily Control Sheets July 2011, 2011 July; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Admissions Desk Daily Control Sheets April 2011, 2011 April; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Admissions Desk Daily Control Sheets May 2011, 2011 May; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Admissions Desk Daily Control Sheets June 2011, 2011 June; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation January 2008, 2008 January; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation November 2007, 2007 November; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation December 2007, 2007 December; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation March 2007, 2007 March; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation April 2007, 2007 April; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation May 2007, 2007 May; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation June 2007, 2007 June; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation July 2007, 2007 July; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation August 2007, 2007 August; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation September 2007, 2007 September; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation October 2007, 2007 October; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation February 2008, 2008 February; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation March 2008, 2008 March; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation April 2008, 2008 April; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation May 2008, 2008 May; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation June 2008, 2008 June; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation July 2008, 2008 July; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation August 2008, 2008 August; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation September 2008, 2008 September; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation October 2008, 2008 October; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation November 2008, 2008 November; Series 15 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Admissions Desk Reconciliation November 2008-January 2009, 2008 November 19 - 2009 January 25; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Admissions Desk July 2009-September 2009, 2009 July 21 - 2009 September 30; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Admissions Desk May 2009-July 2009, 2009 May 20 - 2009 July 23; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Admissions Desk March 2009-May 2009, 2009 March 14 - 2009 May 17; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Admissions Desk November 2009 - March 2010, 2009 November 21 - 2010 March 31; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Admissions Desk Novmeber 2009 - June 2010, 2009 November 18 - 2010 June 17; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Admissions Desk April 2010 - September 2010, 2010 April 3 - 2010 September 13; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Admissions Desk October 2010 - December 2010, 2010 October 7 - 2010 December 12; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Admissions Desk August 2010 - October 2010, 2010 August 1 - 2010 October 1; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Admissions Desk February 2011 - June 2011, 2011 February 24 - 2011 June 30; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Admissions Desk December 2010 - February 2011, 2010 December 15 - 2011 February 23; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Avedon 2 for 1, 2009; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Ticketmaster Invoices 10/2008-12/2008, 2008 October - 2008 December; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Ticketmaster 9/2008-1/2010, 2008 September - 2010 January; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Ticketmaster 12/2008-12/2009, 2008 December - 2009 December; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Daily Sales May-September 2009, 2009 May - 2009 September; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Daily Sales April-December 2008, 2008 April - 2008 December; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Daily Sales September-November 2008, 2008 September - 2008 November; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Daily Sales July-September 2008, 2008 July - 2008 September; Series 15 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Daily Control Sheets August 2010, 2010 August 1; Series 15 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Daily Control Sheets June 2010, 2010 June; Series 15 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Daily Control Sheets May 2010, 2010 May; Series 15 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Daily Control Sheets April 2010, 2010 April; Series 15 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Daily Control Sheets March 2010, 2010 March; Series 15 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Daily Control Sheets December 2009, 2009 December; Series 15 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Daily Control Sheets January-February 2010, 2010 January - 2010 February; Series 15 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Daily Control Sheets November 2009, 2009 November; Series 15 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Daily Control Sheets October 2009, 2009 October; Series 15 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Daily Control Sheets September 2009, 2009 September; Series 15 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Daily Control Sheets August 2009, 2009 August; Series 15 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Daily Control Sheets July 2009, 2009 July; Series 15 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Daily Control Sheets June 2009, 2009 June; Series 15 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Daily Control Sheets May 2009, 2009 May; Series 15 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Daily Control Sheets April 2009, 2009 April 1; Series 15 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Daily Control Sheets March 2009, 2009 March 1; Series 15 (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Audio visual content [2016 processing project], 1969-1977; Series 16
  - Washington Art Series: II Speakers: Sam Gilliam, Marybeth Edelson, Ed Love, 1974 October 30; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - [Unknown Tape], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - [Unknown Audio Tape], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Washington Art: III Baro, Slade, Dorrance Trends in Washington Art - Panel Discussion, 1974 November 6; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Eng: Gaston Neal at Anacostia Musuem Part #3, Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - English AF: 69-76: Gaston Neal Interview, 1969 March 12; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Eng: Shanahan Interview with Roy Slade, Director Corcoran Gallery of Art Regarding 35th Biennial, Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Corcoran/Gertds, 1977 January 23; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - At the Corcoran Gene Davis, 1977 January 30; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Corcoran - Neil MacNeil, 1977 January 16; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Peter Thomas - At the Corcoran, 1977 January 2; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Corcoran Peter Birmingham, Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - At the Corcoran - David Bourdon, Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - African Show Tape, Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Speaker: Dr. Cynthia Field on Architecture: Corcoran Building, 1974 November 4; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Architectural Tour, 1973 July 3; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Washington Art Series: I Speaker: Andrew Hudson Topic: History of Washington Art, 1974 October 23; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Eng: Gaston Neal at Anacostia Musuem Part #1, Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - [Movement Study #1, Movement Study #3, M. Moser], 1977-1978; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - At the Corcoran: Jake Warren Ambassador of Canada, 1977 February 6; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Colette Roberts Double Track, Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - At the Corcoran Muffy Brandon, 1976 December 5; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - At the Corcoran Marcia Tucker of the New Museum, Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - At the Corcoran Frederick Hemmusley, Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - David Lloyd Kreeger, Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Dr. Michael Richman, Daniel Chester French Exhibit, Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Tape #2 Max Protetch, 1977 February 20; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Max Protetch Interview #1, 1977 February 13; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Corcoran Jacob Kainen, 1977 January 9; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Corcoran James Ketchum, 1976 Decemebr 26; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Peter Thomas Director of Corcoran Art School, 1977 January 2; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Paul Jenkins with Karl Fontess, Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Dignac Film by Jose Bermmar, Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - [Unknown Audio Tape], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - [Small Box of Slides], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - At the Corcoran With..., Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - [Cassette Tape 4], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - [Cassette Tape 8], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - The Armand Hammer Collection Corcoran Gallery of Art #776, Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Peter Thomas, 1977 January 2; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - [Cassette Tape 9], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - [Cassette Tape Unknown], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - [Cassette Tape 10], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - [Cassette Tape 11], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - [Cassette Tape 1], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - [Cassette Tape 2], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - [Cassette Tape 12], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - [Cassette Tape 3], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - [Cassette Tape 5], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - [Cassette Tape 6, Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - [Cassette Tape 7], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - [Cassette Tape 14], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - [Cassette Tape 15], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - [Cassette Tape 16], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - [Cassette Tape 17], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - [Loose Papers], Undated; Series 16 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Events files [2016 processing project], 1905,1996-2001; 1996-2001; Series 17
  - [Box of Slides], Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - [Silent Subjects], Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - [Loose Documents], Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Freddie Mac Foundation/Family Day, Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - [Slides & Nature Conservancy Documents], Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Nature Conservancy, Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - TNC, Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - [In Response to Place], 1905 June 23; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - [In Response to Place], 2000-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Checklist, Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - [In Response to Place], Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Terry Evans, 2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Lee Friedlander, 2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Karen Halverson, 1905 June 23; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Misrach, Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Sheikh, 1905 June 22; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - [The Nature Conservancy], Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Sandrow, Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Educator Resource Pack, Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Here is New York, 2002 September 11; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Here is New York: Educator Event, Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - [Loose Documents], Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - The Peale Family Final Report, Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - The Peale Family Family Reunion, Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - The Peale Family Education Resource Materials, Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - The Peale Family Miscellaneous, Circa 1996-2001; Series 17 (Box 48, Folder 26)
- Exhibitions [2016 processing project], 1960-2006; Series 18
  - Thomas Wilfred, Circa 1980-1982; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Karshan Exhibit, Circa 1980-1982; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Karshan Exhibit, Circa 1980-1982; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Melzac Exhibit, Circa 1980-1982; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Eleanor Dickinson, Circa 1980-1982; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Kaleidoscope: a creative art experience for children, Circa 1980-1982; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Tour Requests & Attendance 1960-1962, Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1964/65 Statistical Reports, 1964-1965; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Education Copy for Docent Use 1969-71, 1969-1971; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Finances Fiscal 1969-1970, Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Docent Records 1969-70, 1969-1970; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Staff Regulations 1969, Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - CGA Improving The New Organizational Structure May 1969, 1969 May; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - CSA Report & Recommendations 1968-69, 1968-1969; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Department of Education Reports, 1968-1970; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Letters to Schools 1969, Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 1969 - Education Materials, Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Children's Galleryy 1969-70, 1969-1970; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Museum Educator's Roundtable 1969-70, 1969-1970; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Weekend Docents 1969-70, 1969-1970; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Docent Training 1971-72, 1971-1972; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Finances 1971-72, 1971-1972; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Tour Information 1970-71, 1970-1971; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - 1971 Teacher Evaluation of Tour, Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Washington Area Union Organizing Attempt - 1971, Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Sandak Invoices, Circa 1980-1982; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Sandak - Correspondence, Circa 1980-1982; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Past Shows: Wilderness, 1971, Circa 1980-1982; Series 18 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - A. Hammer: 4 Centuries of Masterpieces fall, 1980, Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - In Other Words, 1986 May 9 - June 29; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Niagara Pamphlet, Circa 1987-1988; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Italian Rennaissance Maiolica, Circa 1987-1988; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Italian Rennaissance Maiolica, Circa 1987-1988; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Drawn Out, Circa 1987-1988; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - L'Amour Fou, Circa 1987-1988; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Friends Of The Corcoran 25th Anniversary Exhibition, Circa 1987-1988; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Spectrum / Art Talk, Circa 1987-1988; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Ross / Willis, Circa 1987-1988; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Assortment of Pamphlets, Circa 1987-1988; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Borofsky, Circa 1987-1988; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Teachers' Brochure, Circa 1987-1988; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Lichtenstein Self Tours 1988, Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - The Indelible Image Brochure, Circa 1987-1988; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - American Masters: Works on Paper from the CGA Education Programs, Circa 1987-1988; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Shaker Design, Circa 1987-1988; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Odyssey: The Art of Photography at National Geographic, Circa 1987-1988; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Joan Mitchell 2/27-7/1/87, 1987; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - New World: Acoustiguide, Circa 1987-1988; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - New World Correspondence, Circa 1987-1988; Series 18 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Exhibit Summary Sheets, Circa 1978-1980; Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - William Christenberry: Southern Views (1983), Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Expressions/Accents (Summer 84), 1984; Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Leonardo's Codex Leicester - L.A., Circa 1978-1980; Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Corcoran Visitors Guide, Circa 1978-1980; Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Spectrum, Circa 1978-1980; Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Armand Hammer Brochures, Circa 1978-1980; Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Discover the Corcoran, Circa 1978-1980; Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Leonardo's Codex Leicester - CGA Show, Circa 1978-1980; Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Goya, Circa 1978-1980; Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Of Time and Place Brochures, 1981 September-November; Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 1999 Biennial - DeKooning, Circa 1978-1980; Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 1979 Biennial - J. John, Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 1979 Biennial - Rauschenberg, Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 1979 Biennial - Lichtenstein, Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - 1979 Biennial - Kelly, Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Black Folk Art Brochures, 1982; Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Cartier - Bresson Exhib. School Unit, 1981 April; Series 18 (Box 8, Folder 18)